CORIYON ARRINGTON

Minneapolis, MN 55422 | coriyonarrington@gmail.com | linked.com/in/coriyon | coriyon.com | (612) 466-0228

Summary

I'm a Senior Product Designer with 4+ years of experience in human-centered design. What sets me apart is my background in Biomedical Engineering. I'm passionate about inspiring people to lead healthier lives daily. My specialty is finding solutions that meet user needs and achieve business objectives. My unique approach combines strategy, technology, and creativity.

Top Skills

Interpersonal

Communication, Problem-Solving, Storytelling, Leadership, Empathy, Collaboration, Presenting, Teamwork

Industry

User Research, User Experience Design, User Interface Design, Interaction Design, Information Architecture, Visual Design, Prototyping, Design Systems, Analytics, Usability Testing, Wireframes, HTML/CSS

Tools

Figma, Maze, Miro, Whimsical, Notion, Jira, Mixpanel, Notion, UsabilityHub

Education

UX/UI Design

Thinkful (acquired Bloc) 11/2019 - 08/2020

BS, Biomedical Engineering

East Carolina University 08/2010 - 05/2015

Professional Experience

Senior Product Designer

UX Scholars | 01/2023 - Present

- Created a community of over 60+ entrylevel UX designers and career changers
- Mentored and coached 5+ junior to midlevel designers, facilitating their growth
- Started a newsletter for UX professionals resulting in 180 subscribers in 3 months
- Became the organizer for a Meetup group of 230+ UX/UI designers in Minneapolis
- Joined UXPA of Minnesota a professional group with over 700 members

Product Designer

Manifold Group | 01/2021 - 01/2023

- Shipped 5+ high-quality software products by collaborating with clients, SMEs, engineers, marketers, and PMs
- Redesigned a mobile app to engage patients throughout their rehab journey, increasing patient motivation at 3 facilities
- Launched a web app that helps clinicians collaborate and provide care saving 1.5 hours per clinician each week
- Interviewed 20+ key stakeholders to translate pain points and goals into intuitive product design decisions
- Contributed to team ops by establishing
 5+ standard operating procedures